chameleon.ad 2018-09-03

# Chameleon.ad > Privacy Policy

Chameleon have compiled the information that is collected because we are interested to feel safe when visiting our pages. 

**1\. Personal Data**

Personal Data is the information such as your name, your address, your telephone number and your payments info. You can visit our pages without providing personal information. As a standard procedure, our web servers temporarily record the connection data of the enquiring computer. But the data is used in anonymous (also IP address) for internal statistics and for the development of the website. 

Personal Data isn't collected unless you provide this information voluntarily for the registration to our network. Personal Data is used by us for the technical administration of the website and for the conctract concluded with you. We protect your data against unauthorised access by third parties. 

If you have provided us, we can use your data for advertising and market purposes. 

Your personal data will not be forwarded to third parties, unless this is necessary for the execution of a contract or if you have given your specific consent to this. 

**2\. Cookies**

Cookies are browser files that we stored only to know the number of users in our pages and offer a good service for you. 

You can also use our offers without cookies. Under Tools/Internet Options in your respective browser you can deactivate the storing of cookies, limit this to specific websites or set your browser such that it informs you as soon as a cookie is sent. You can also delete cookies from the hard drive of your PC at any time (e.g. Firefox: Tools > Options > Privacy > Show Cookies > Remove Cookie / Remove All Cookies; Internet Explorer: Tools > Internet Options > Delete Browsing History / Cookies). Chameleon domains: www.chameleon.ad, static.chameleon.ad. Please note, however, that when so doing you must reckon with restricted presentation of the site and limited user guidance. 

**3\. Security**

Chameleon takes all security measures to protect your data against unauthorised access. Your data are saved in secure operating environment wich aren't visible by the public. When you login / signup in our network your personal data will be transmitted in encrypted form. 

**4\. Other**

You can obtain, modify or delete information stored about you any time. We have to delete your personal data stored automatically if this data is no necessary for the purpose for wich it was stored or if storage of this data isn't permitted for legal reasons. 

For information, suggestions or complaints you can contact us: 

**Email to** [support@chameleon.ad](mailto:support@chameleon.ad)   
**or** Chameleon Advertising Technologies LTD - The Black Church, St. Mary's Place - Dublin 07 - Ireland
